{
    "subject": "resource/Marisa_Pavan",
    "predicate": "property/children",
    "object": "Jean-Claude Aumont",
    "human_readable": "Marisa Pavan has children named Jean-Claude Aumont.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9885530471801758,
            "question": "Is Jean-Claude Aumont a child of Marisa Pavan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9843214750289917,
            "question": "Is Jean-Claude Aumont's parent Marisa Pavan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9764818549156189,
            "question": "Does Jean-Claude Aumont belong to Marisa Pavan's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9569949507713318,
            "question": "Name a child of Marisa Pavan."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.914955735206604,
            "question": "Who are Marisa Pavan's children?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.896315336227417,
            "question": "What is the name of one of Marisa Pavan's children?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8875060081481934,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Marisa Pavan and Jean-Claude Aumont?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8398847579956055,
            "question": "Who are Jean-Claude Aumont's parents?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7225608825683594,
            "question": "How many children does Marisa Pavan have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3964879810810089,
            "question": "Marisa Pavan is the mother of...?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Marisa Pavan has children named Jean-Claude Aumont.",
            "html": "dbpedia_668_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How many children does Marisa Pavan have?",
            "html": "dbpedia_668_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are Jean-Claude Aumont's parents?",
            "html": "dbpedia_668_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the relationship between Marisa Pavan and Jean-Claude Aumont?",
            "html": "dbpedia_668_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_668_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_668_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_668_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_668_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_668_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_668_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_668_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_668_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_668_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_668_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Marisa Pavan had two sons, Jean-Claude and Patrick. Therefore, the information supports the triple stating that Marisa Pavan has children named Jean-Claude Aumont."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}